as a society we are so addicted to this
consumerism and which of course means
were addicted to the resources that come
from that are required and the oil and
energy are also addicted to negativity
and media and I don't think like every
other addiction telling people to just
not do it is it really helpful
especially when it's overwhelming I mean
I do care where my dollars are spent I
care very much where I vote and yet it's
overwhelming to have the amount of
knowledge that I would need to make
informed logical decisions doesn't exist
right now and so I propose we do it
together that we figure out what
knowledge is needed to know that I think
the answer to most addictions